<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>The Homework Life</title>
		<link>http://www.thehomeworklife.co.nf</link>
		<description>The joys and pains of a high school career.</description>
		<item><title>RSS, GitHub, and SVGs</title><link>http://www.thehomeworklife.co.nf/index.html?post=73</link><description>The Homework Life is one step closer to becoming a more widely supported blog with RSS feeds! Now, you can subscribe to the feed by simply giving the link to a feed reader, such as FeedReader. It allows you to easily see the ten most recent posts wit...</description><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 22:04:00 +0200</pubDate></item><item><title>Bump</title><link>http://www.thehomeworklife.co.nf/index.html?post=72</link><description>Bump.That's how they do it, right? Revive a blog post? Spark some interest into a community driven by the present? A present that is always burying the past? The past that is full of virtuous mistakes and the subsequent lessons?And that's what I hope...</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 23:51:00 +0200</pubDate></item><item><title>General Status Update</title><link>http://www.thehomeworklife.co.nf/index.html?post=71</link><description>CodingI've got another one. Based off of Jacob Wunder's Tap Tap Pop! (which was based off of Pop the Lock), here is my own version of Pop the Lock. It's arguably very simple, minimalistic, and feature-less ; but it captures the main essence of the ga...</description><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 18:56:00 +0200</pubDate></item><item><title>A Tutorial Lesson, Animated Circles, and Educational Programs</title><link>http://www.thehomeworklife.co.nf/index.html?post=70</link><description>I worked with the new Programming Club after school today. An alumni worked us through a simple webpage themed like his webpage that used jQuery to position and animate. It was quite interesting, and I learned a simple, mathematical way to animate it...</description><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 22:18:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>New Web Apps!</title><link>http://www.thehomeworklife.co.nf/index.html?post=69</link><description>I've posted a new little web application, Speller Bee. I know that it should be "Spelling Bee," but that name was taken on Heroku (where the Node.js server is hosted) and therefore I chose something a little different to spice it up.It comes with all...</description><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 23:25:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Tarnish</title><link>http://www.thehomeworklife.co.nf/index.html?post=68</link><description>If you've ever been an overextended, perfectionist high-school teenager, you'd understand. The homework life that I live is beginning to feel unattainable. In the end, you have to reach a compromise between quality and quantity. It's becoming a fact ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 16:11:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Site Mixups!</title><link>http://www.thehomeworklife.co.nf/index.html?post=67</link><description>img.rounded{border-radius:100%;width:250px;max-width:100%}table#newUpdateTable td:nth-of-type(1){width:250px;max-width:50%}table#newUpdateTable td{padding:10px 20px}There have been many major site improvements I made today! Many are graphical changes...</description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 00:06:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>From Written Words to Spoken Meaning</title><link>http://www.thehomeworklife.co.nf/index.html?post=66</link><description>What do I believe? Check it out at "As of February 2016", a poem based off of "As of May 2002" by Del Shortliffe1.And another piece I have recently written, this time in response to Catcher in the Rye, is "Little Chained Bird", a little vignette that...</description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 00:31:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Stampede!</title><link>http://www.thehomeworklife.co.nf/index.html?post=64</link><description>I would be a student council officer for two reasons only: to have a leadership role for the National Honor Society, and to stop prom from soaking up all the students’ money. Because, as a whole, fundraising does eventually end up going towards our...</description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 22:49:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>Back to Coding and Posting!</title><link>http://www.thehomeworklife.co.nf/index.html?post=63</link><description>Sorry for the lack of posting in the past few days. I have been busy with other projects, especially with Node.js, an amazing JavaScript platform. It's extremely confusing and frustrating right now, but I'm managing to slowly work my way through and ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 17:54:00 +0100</pubDate></item>
	</channel>
</rss>